Did you know that a commerce firm saw 28%
rising orders in the first two days of the
festival season. This is possible
because in India demand is more than ₹4,000 crore. There are
150 million online
shops. So, if you buy something online, the
parcel comes to your city or local
warehouse, which is then sorted at a facility center and
delivered to your home.
This means that the
logistics and transportation companies involved in the entire delivery process are
also growing. Are they? Now
you must be wondering, can you be a
part of this growth story? The answer is very
simple. Just today, ICICI
Prudential Transportation and UGCIS
Info Classes are on 20th October 2020. Mutual
Fund Devesh Bazar is under risk.
Read all the documents related to the scheme carefully.